A Musical Adaptation of Mark Twain's Tom Sawyer
Tom Sawyer is a family, music, adventure film directed by Don Taylor.
Tom Sawyer and his pal Huckleberry Finn have great adventures on the Mississippi River,
pretending to be pirates, attending their own funeral, and witnessing a murder.
Tom Sawyer, played by Johnny Whitaker.
Tia Polly, played by Celeste Holm.
Muff Potter, played by Warren Oates.
Huckleberry Finn, played by Jeff East.
Becky Thatcher, played by Jodie Foster.
Widder Douglas, played by Lucille Benson.
Tom Sawyer is the 1973 American musical film adaptation of the Mark Twain novel
The Adventures of Tom Sawyer and was directed by Don Taylor.
The film was produced by Reader's Digest in collaboration with Arthur P.
Jacobs, and its screenplay and songs were written
by the Sherman Brothers, Robert B.
Sherman and Richard M.
During the 46th Academy Awards, the film received three nominations for Best Original Song
Score, Best Art Direction, and Best Costume Design, but failed to win any.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
missouri, musical, 19th century.
The tone is lighthearted.